Guide to the International Association for Cultural Freedom Records 1941-1978
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: Correspondence and Subject Files
  - Subseries I: Correspondence and Subject Files, 1948-1967
    - Sub-subseries 12: "L"
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Cuba, 1955 (Box 223, Folder 7)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Mexico, 1955 (Box 223, Folder 8)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Uruguay, 1955 (Box 223, Folder 9)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Argentina, 1955-1956 (Box 223, Folder 10)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Argentina, 1955-1956 (Box 223, Folder 11)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Argentina, 1959 (Box 223, Folder 12)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Brazil-Chile, 1955-1956 (Box 224, Folder 1)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Chile, 1955-1956 (Box 224, Folder 2)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Cuba, 1955-1956 (Box 224, Folder 3)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, France, 1950-1956 (Box 224, Folder 4)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Mexico, 1956 (Box 224, Folder 5)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Mexico, 1956 (Box 224, Folder 6)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Peru-Uruguay, 1956 (Box 224, Folder 7)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Argentina, 1958 (Box 224, Folder 8)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Brazil, 1958 (Box 224, Folder 9)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Brazil, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Brazil, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Brazil, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Brazil, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Cuba, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 5)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, France, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 6)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Mexico, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 7)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Mexico, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 8)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Peru, 1957-1958 (Box 225, Folder 9)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Uruguay, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 10)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Venezuela, 1958 (Box 225, Folder 11)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Argentina, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 1)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Argentina, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 2)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Brazil, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 3)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Chile, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 4)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Chile, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 5)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Chile, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 6)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Cuba, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 7)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, France, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 8)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Mexico, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 9)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Peru, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 10)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Peru, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 11)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Spain, 1959 (Box 226, Folder 12)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Spain, 1959 (Box 227, Folder 1)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Spain, 1959 (Box 227, Folder 2)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Uruguay, 1959 (Box 227, Folder 3)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Argentina, 1959-1960 (Box 227, Folder 4)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Argentina, 1959-1960 (Box 227, Folder 5)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Brazil, 1960-1961 (Box 227, Folder 6)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Chile, 1960 (Box 227, Folder 7)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Cuba, 1960 (Box 227, Folder 8)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Ecuador, 1960 (Box 227, Folder 9)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, France, 1960 (Box 227, Folder 10)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Mexico, 1960 (Box 227, Folder 11)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Peru, 1960 (Box 228, Folder 1)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Spain, 1960 (Box 228, Folder 2)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, United States- Venezuela, 1960 (Box 228, Folder 3)
      - Latin American Press Clippings, Latin American Bureau, 1953-1959 (Box 228, Folder 4)
      - Latin American Composers Contest Jury, 1963 (Box 228, Folder 5)
      - Latin America- Seymour, Lawrence, 1959-1962 (Box 228, Folder 6)
      - Latin America- Seymour, Lawrence, 1963-1966 (Box 228, Folder 7)
      - Lebanon, 1960-1961 (Box 228, Folder 8)
      - Lebanon, 1962 (Box 228, Folder 9)
      - Lebanon, 1962 (Box 228, Folder 10)
      - Lebanon, 1963-1964 (Box 229, Folder 1)
      - Lebanon, 1965-1967 (Box 229, Folder 2)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1954 (Box 229, Folder 3)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1955 (Box 229, Folder 4)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1956 (Box 229, Folder 5)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1956 (Box 229, Folder 6)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1957 (Box 229, Folder 7)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1957 (Box 229, Folder 8)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara- Teheran Conference, 1957 (Box 230, Folder 1)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1958 (Box 230, Folder 2)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1959 (Box 230, Folder 3)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1959 (Box 230, Folder 4)
      - Lebanon, Ghorayeb, Beshara, 1960-1967 (Box 230, Folder 5)
      - Lebanon, Press Clippings, 1956 (Box 230, Folder 6)
      - Lebanon, Press Clippings, 1956 (Box 230, Folder 7)
      - Lebanon, Press Clippings, 1958 (Box 230, Folder 8)
      - Lebanon, Hiwar magazine, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 9)
      - Lebanon, Hiwar magazine, 1963 (Box 230, Folder 10)
      - Lebanon, Hiwar magazine, 1964 (Box 230, Folder 11)
      - Lebanon, Hiwar magazine, 1965 (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - Lebanon, Hiwar magazine, 1965 (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Lebanon, Hiwar magazine, 1966 (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - Lebanon, Hiwar magazine, 1967 (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - Lebanon Committee Press Clippings, 1954 (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - Lewis, Arthur, 1956 (Box 231, Folder 6)
      - Lewis, Arthur, 1956 (Box 231, Folder 7)
      - Lewis, Arthur, 1957 (Box 231, Folder 8)
      - Lewis, Arthur, 1958-1967 (Box 231, Folder 9)
      - Lewis, Arthur- Tokyo Conference, 1956-1957 (Box 231, Folder 10)
      - Lewis, Arthur- Tokyo Conference, 1956-1957 (Box 231, Folder 11)
      - Library of International Studies, 1961-1964 (Box 231, Folder 12)
      - Liebermann, Rolf, 1956-1957 (Box 231, Folder 13)
      - Lowenthal, Richard, 1957-1960 (Box 231, Folder 14)
      - Luce International Press Clipping Service, 1957-1961 (Box 231, Folder 15)
      - Lüthy, Herbert, 1951-1960 (Box 231, Folder 16)
    - Sub-subseries 13: "M"
      - General Correspondence "M," 1950-1951 (Box 232, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1952-1955 (Box 232, Folder 2)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1956 (Box 232, Folder 3)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1957 (Box 232, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1957 (Box 232, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1958 (Box 232, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1959 (Box 232, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1960 (Box 232, Folder 8)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1961 (Box 232, Folder 9)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1962 (Box 232, Folder 10)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1963 (Box 232, Folder 11)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1964 (Box 233, Folder 1)
      - General Correspondence "M," 1965-1966 (Box 233, Folder 2)
      - MacCrindle-McVey Correspondence, 1961-1966 (Box 233, Folder 3)
      - McAuley, James, 1959-1960 (Box 233, Folder 4)
      - Macauley, Robie, 1959-1962 (Box 233, Folder 5)
      - Macauley, Robie, 1963-1964 (Box 233, Folder 6)
      - Macauley, Robie,, 1965-1966 (Box 233, Folder 7)
      - MacDonald, Dwight, 1955 (Box 233, Folder 8)
      - MacDonald, Dwight, 1956-1965 (Box 233, Folder 9)
      - McGrady, Pat, 1957-1959 (Box 233, Folder 10)
      - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1954-1955 (Box 233, Folder 11)
      - McGregor, Marian, 1959 (Box 233, Folder 12)
      - McLean, Donald, 1956-1958 (Box 233, Folder 13)
      - de Madariaga, Salvador, 1950-1951 (Box 233, Folder 14)
      - de Madariaga, Salvador, 1953-1955 (Box 233, Folder 15)
      - de Madariaga, Salvador, 1956-1960 (Box 233, Folder 16)
      - de Madariaga, Salvador, 1957 (Box 233, Folder 17)
      - de Madariaga, Salvador, 1961 (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - de Madariaga, Salvador, 1962-1966 (Box 234, Folder 2)
      - de Madariaga, Salvador, Press Clippings, 1957 (Box 234, Folder 2a)
      - de Madariaga, Salvador manuscript, undated (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Mankour, Ibrahim, 1959-1961 (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - Mankour, Ibrahim, 1962-1966 (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - Maison de la Liberté, 1959-1960 (Box 234, Folder 6)
      - Malaysia, 1964-1966 (Box 234, Folder 7)
      - Malraux- Mansouroff, 1954-1965 (Box 234, Folder 8)
      - Martin, Christopher, 1960 (Box 234, Folder 9)
      - Martin, Kurt, 1956 (Box 234, Folder 10)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1952-1953 (Box 234, Folder 11)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1953 (Box 234, Folder 12)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1953 (Box 234, Folder 13)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1954 (Box 234, Folder 14)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1954 (Box 235, Folder 1)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1955 (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1955 (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1956 (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1956 (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1956 (Box 235, Folder 6)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1957 (Box 235, Folder 7)
      - Masani, Minoo, 1957 (Box 235, Folder 8)
      - Masani, Minoo, Second Annual Conference of Indian Committee for Cultural Freedom, 1953 (Box 235, Folder 9)
      - Masani, Minoo, Papers on Indian planning, 1955-1956 (Box 235, Folder 10)
      - Masani, Minoo, Pan-Asiatic Conference, 1952 (Box 235, Folder 11)
      - Maulnier, Thierry, 1954 (Box 235, Folder 12)
      - M.B.A.R.I.(African Writers' and Artists' Club), 1962-1963 (Box 235, Folder 13)
      - M.B.A.R.I. (African Writers' and Artists' Club), 1964-1966 (Box 236, Folder 1)
      - Meray, Tibor, 1958-1960 (Box 236, Folder 2)
      - Meray, Tibor, 1961-1966 (Box 236, Folder 3)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis, 1961-1962 (Box 236, Folder 4)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis, 1963 (Box 236, Folder 5)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis, 1963 (Box 236, Folder 6)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis, 1963 (Box 236, Folder 7)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis, 1964 (Box 236, Folder 8)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis, 1964 (Box 236, Folder 9)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis, 1965-1966 (Box 236, Folder 10)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis and Keith Botsford, Reports on Latin America, 1963 (Box 236, Folder 11)
      - Mercier, Vega Luis and Keith Botsford, Reports on Latin America, 1963 (Box 237, Folder 1)
      - Merrill, Charles, 1961-1963 (Box 237, Folder 2)
      - Merrill, Charles, 1964-1967 (Box 237, Folder 3)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Delegates "A-C," 1956 (Box 237, Folder 4)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Delegates "C-H," 1956 (Box 237, Folder 5)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Delegates "M-P," 1956 (Box 237, Folder 6)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Delegates "S-Z," 1956 (Box 237, Folder 7)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 237, Folder 8)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 237, Folder 9)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 237, Folder 10)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 237, Folder 11)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Conference Papers, 1956 (Box 237, Folder 12)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Conference Papers, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 1)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Conference Papers, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 2)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Conference Papers, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 3)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Conference Papers, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 4)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Press Clippings, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 5)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Press Clippings, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 6)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Press Clippings, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 7)
      - Mexico, Conferencia Interamericana de Mexico, Press Clippings, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 8)
      - Mexico, Mexico City Conference, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 9)
      - Mexico, Mexico City Conference, 1956 (Box 238, Folder 10)
      - Mexico, Press Clippings, 1959 (Box 238, Folder 10a)
      - Middle East, 1959-1964 (Box 238, Folder 11)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "A," 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 1)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "B," 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 2)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "C-E," 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 3)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "F-H," 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 4)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "H," 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 5)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "H-J," 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 6)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "J," 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 7)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Jargy, Simon, 1964 (Box 239, Folder 8)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Jargy, Simon, 1965 (Box 239, Folder 9)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Jargy, Simon, 1966 (Box 239, Folder 10)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Jargy, Simon- Progress Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 239, Folder 11)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "J-L," 1963-1966 (Box 239, Folder 12)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "L," 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 1)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "L-M," 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 2)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "M," 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 3)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "M-Q," 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 4)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Press Clippings, 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 5)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Press Clippings, 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 6)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Press Clippings, 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 7)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "R," 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 8)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "S," 1963-1966 (Box 240, Folder 9)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Sayigh, Tawfiq, 1962 (Box 240, Folder 10)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Sayigh, Tawfiq, 1963 (Box 240, Folder 11)
      - Middle East- Topic Files- Sayigh, Tawfiq, 1964-1966 (Box 241, Folder 1)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "S," 1963-1966 (Box 241, Folder 2)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "S," 1963-1966 (Box 241, Folder 3)
      - Middle East- Topic Files "T-Z," 1963-1966 (Box 241, Folder 4)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Public Letters and Speeches, 1964-1965 (Box 241, Folder 5)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Articles, 1964-1965 (Box 241, Folder 6)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Articles, 1964-1965 (Box 241, Folder 7)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Articles, 1964-1965 (Box 241, Folder 8)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Press Clippings, 1965 (Box 241, Folder 9)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Press Clippings, 1965 (Box 242, Folder 1)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Leo Labedz- Progress Reports, 1965 (Box 242, Folder 2)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Leo Labedz- Progress Reports, 1965 (Box 242, Folder 3)
      - Mihajlov, Mihajlo- Leo Labedz- Progress Reports, 1965 (Box 242, Folder 4)
      - Milosz, Czeslaw, 1951-1956 (Box 242, Folder 5)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1956-1957 (Box 242, Folder 6)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1958-1959 (Box 242, Folder 7)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1959 (Box 242, Folder 8)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1960 (Box 242, Folder 9)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1960 (Box 243, Folder 1)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1960 (Box 243, Folder 2)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1960 (Box 243, Folder 3)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1960 (Box 243, Folder 4)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1960 (Box 243, Folder 5)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1960 (Box 243, Folder 6)
      - Mindlin, Meir, 1961 (Box 243, Folder 7)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1962 (Box 243, Folder 8)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1962 (Box 243, Folder 9)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1962 (Box 243, Folder 10)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1963 (Box 243, Folder 11)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1963 (Box 243, Folder 12)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1963 (Box 243, Folder 13)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1964 (Box 244, Folder 1)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1964 (Box 244, Folder 2)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1964 (Box 244, Folder 3)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1965 (Box 244, Folder 4)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Forum Service, 1966 (Box 244, Folder 5)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Censorship, 1965 (Box 244, Folder 6)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Censorship, 1966 (Box 244, Folder 7)
      - Mindlin, Meir- Congress News, 1966 (Box 244, Folder 8)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "A-F," 1962 (Box 244, Folder 9)
      - Minerva - Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "G-M," 1962 (Box 244, Folder 10)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "M-R," 1962 (Box 245, Folder 1)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "S-Z," 1962 (Box 245, Folder 2)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion, 1962 (Box 245, Folder 3)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "A-D," 1963 (Box 245, Folder 4)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "E-L," 1963 (Box 245, Folder 5)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "M-R," 1963 (Box 245, Folder 6)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "A-H," 1964 (Box 245, Folder 7)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "I-M," 1964 (Box 245, Folder 8)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "N-Z," 1964 (Box 246, Folder 1)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion, 1964 (Box 246, Folder 2)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion, 1964 (Box 246, Folder 3)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion, 1965 (Box 246, Folder 4)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "A-H," 1965 (Box 246, Folder 5)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "I-Q," 1965 (Box 246, Folder 6)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Bieber, Marion "R-Z," 1965 (Box 246, Folder 7)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 246, Folder 8)
      - Minerva, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 246, Folder 9)
      - Minerva, Manuscripts, 1961-1965 (Box 247, Folder 1)
      - Minerva, Manuscripts, 1965 (Box 247, Folder 2)
      - Minerva, Manuscripts, undated (Box 247, Folder 3)
      - Minerva, Manuscripts, undated (Box 247, Folder 4)
      - Minerva, Manuscripts, undated (Box 247, Folder 5)
      - Minerva, Manuscripts "A-D," 1965 (Box 247, Folder 6)
      - Minerva, Manuscripts "E-L," 1966 (Box 247, Folder 7)
      - Minerva, Manuscripts "M-Z," 1965 (Box 247, Folder 8)
      - Minerva, Memoranda "A-G," 1962 (Box 248, Folder 1)
      - Minerva, Memoranda "H-P," 1962 (Box 248, Folder 2)
      - Minerva, Memoranda "Q-Z," 1962 (Box 248, Folder 3)
      - Minerva, Miscellaneous Documents, 1964-1966 (Box 248, Folder 4)
      - Minerva, Press Clippings, 1965 (Box 248, Folder 5)
      - Minerva, Press Clippings, 1965 (Box 248, Folder 6)
      - Minerva, Press Clippings, 1966 (Box 248, Folder 7)
      - Minerva, Press Clippings, Boggio, Samuel, 1964-1965 (Box 248, Folder 8)
      - Minerva, Press Clippings, Boggio, Samuel, 1964-1965 (Box 248, Folder 9)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 249, Folder 1)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1954 (Box 249, Folder 2)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1955 (Box 249, Folder 3)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1956 (Box 249, Folder 4)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1956 (Box 249, Folder 5)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1957 (Box 249, Folder 6)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1957 (Box 249, Folder 7)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1957 (Box 249, Folder 8)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 250, Folder 1)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 250, Folder 2)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1958 (Box 250, Folder 3)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 250, Folder 4)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1959 (Box 250, Folder 5)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1960 (Box 250, Folder 6)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1961 (Box 250, Folder 7)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1962 (Box 250, Folder 8)
      - Der Monat- Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 250, Folder 9)
      - Der Monat- Advertising and Circulation, 1962-1966 (Box 250, Folder 10)
      - Der Monat- Audit Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 250, Folder 11)
      - Der Monat- Financial, 1962-1963 (Box 250, Folder 12)
      - Der Monat- Financial, 1964 (Box 250, Folder 13)
      - Der Monat- Financial, 1965 (Box 250, Folder 14)
      - Der Monat- Financial, 1966-1967 (Box 250, Folder 15)
      - Morandi, Luigi, 1954-1958 (Box 251, Folder 1)
      - Muggeridge, Malcolm, 1955-1956 (Box 251, Folder 2)
      - Muggeridge, Malcolm, 1957-1959 (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - Sub-subseries 14: "N"
      - General Correspondence "N," undated (Box 251, Folder 4)
      - General Correspondence "N," 1954-1956 (Box 251, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence "N," 1957-1958 (Box 251, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence "N," 1959-1961 (Box 251, Folder 7)
      - General Correspondence "N," 1962-1966 (Box 251, Folder 8)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 251, Folder 9)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 251, Folder 10)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1953 (Box 251, Folder 11)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 251, Folder 12)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1954 (Box 251, Folder 13)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "A-D," 1954 (Box 252, Folder 1)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "E-L," 1954 (Box 252, Folder 2)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "M-Q," 1954 (Box 252, Folder 3)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "R-Z," 1954 (Box 252, Folder 4)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "A-C," 1955 (Box 252, Folder 5)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "D-G," 1955 (Box 252, Folder 6)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "H-Z," 1955 (Box 252, Folder 7)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 252, Folder 8)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "A-E," 1956 (Box 252, Folder 9)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "F-M," 1956 (Box 252, Folder 10)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "N-O," 1956 (Box 253, Folder 1)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence "P-Z," 1956 (Box 253, Folder 2)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, Insurance, 1956 (Box 253, Folder 3)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1957 (Box 253, Folder 4)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1958 (Box 253, Folder 5)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 253, Folder 6)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 253, Folder 7)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 253, Folder 8)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Correspondence, Dallapiccola-Sabura, 1955-1958 (Box 253, Folder 9)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Music Conference in Asia, 1956 (Box 253, Folder 10)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Music Conference in Asia- Piovesan, Alessandro, 1957-1958 (Box 253, Folder 11)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Music Conference in Asia- Pitt and Scott, Ltd., 1955-1956 (Box 253, Folder 12)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, Music Conference in Asia- Shankar, Ravi, 1956-1957 (Box 253, Folder 13)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, International Secretariat, 1950 (Box 253, Folder 14)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, International Secretariat, 1950 (Box 253, Folder 15)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, International Secretariat, January 1951 (Box 254, Folder 1)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, International Secretariat, January 1951 (Box 254, Folder 2)
      - Nabokov, Nicolas, International Secretariat, February 1951 (Box 254, Folder 3)